FASAN OLUWABUKOLA AJIKE

Royal Garden Estate, Ajah, Lagos State, Nigeria. oluwabukola.fasan@gmail.com 08080110323, 07065103467 Portfolio

Career Objective

I am a passionate front-end developer willing to contribute to the efficiency of the team via commitment, hard work, attention to detail, and superior organisational abilities. I have expertise in web development and UI/UX design as well as a thorough grasp of computers.

Skills

- HTML
- Figma and Corel Draw.
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- React
- Next

Education

B.SC Computer Science (Second Class Upper Division)

Federal University Oye- Ekiti, Ekiti state. 2015-2019

• Other Certifications

Mobile App Development

Women Techsters Program, Tech4Dev, Lagos State. 2022-2023

Software Development (Front-end Development)

Stutern, Lagos State. 2022-2023

Certificate of Completion (Product Design)

Zuri Inc., Lagos State. 2022

Certificate in Introduction to UI/UX

Geneza School of design, Lagos State. 2022

Experience

☐ Front-End Developer Startup Hive, Lagos State, Nigeria

January 2024-March 2024

- Translating UI/UX designs into actual codes using Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Typescript, and Shaden UI
- To build reusable codes and functional systems.
- Collaborated with full-stack developers, specialising in frontend development, database management, and testing.
- contributing to software applications by designing user interfaces, implementing server-side logic,

☐ Front-End Developer Intern Sabi Programmers, Akure, Ondo State, Nigeria

July 2023- November 2023

- Translating UI/UX designs into actual codes using HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, and React.
- To build reusable codes and functional systems.
- Building the client's side of the web application.
- Collaborating with Product Designers, Back-end Designers, and Project Managers to improve user experience.
- Working closely with backend developers to integrate front-end components with server-side logic.

☐ UI/UX Designer

Onract Limited, Manchester, England, United Kingdom (Remote).

December 2022- December 2023

- Gather and evaluate user requirements in collaboration with product managers and engineers.
- Develop UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look like.
- Adhere to style standards on fonts, colours and images.
- Develop UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and would look like.

☐ Product Designer (Intern) Zuri Inc-Ingressive for Good, Africa.

March 2022- June 2022

- Designed a Mobile Management system for task management
- Conducted User Research on Logistics Industry
- Team collaboration on the designing authentication codes Library